Finding aid for the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archive Collection of Audio Materials, 1970-1999 LSC.2230
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Liz Maines Gay Radio Show KFCF 88.1, 1994; Series 18.; 17 audio cassette tapes
  - It's A Queer Thang: Ken Frees GL Film Festival, [ca. 1990s]; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 15)
    Side 1: Hosts Liz Maines and Jeff Robinson interview Ken Frees of the Fresno International Gay and Lesbian Entertainment in Arts and Film, the organization that hosts the Gay and Lesbian Film Festival/Fresno Reel Pride Film Festival. They discuss the organization's origins, purpose, volunteer opportunities, and all that involved in putting together a film festival. Side 2: Hosts Liz Maines and Tom Brandenberry interview Diana Stanley and Jerry Ward from the Fresno chapter of Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG). They discuss PFLAG's origins and purpose, as well as local activities and events they have planned.
  - It's A Queer Thang: Gay and Lesbian Sensitivity Training, March 1994; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 16)
    Hosts Liz Maines, Tom Brandenberry, and Jeff Robinson interview Barbara Cooper from the Community Links Speaker's Bureau. The group conducts lesbian and gay sensitivity training at organizations throughout the Fresno area, including schools, universities, and police stations.
  - It's A Queer Thang: News and Discussion, June 1994; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 17)
    Hosts Liz Maines, Tom Brandenberry, and Jeff Robinson provide major gay and lesbian related news and discuss implications. The episode is Tom Brandenberry's last show.
- June L Mazer and Bunny MacCulloch Interviews Etc., 1981-1990; Series 4.; 17 audio cassette tapes
  Interviews with June Mazer and Bunny MacCulloch concerning the SCWU, the archive, Mazer's death and lesbian culture in the San Francisco Bay Area.
  - Bunny MacCulloch interviewed by June Mazer on Before Stonewall, 1 March 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 1)
    Discussion of the documentary Before Stonewall
  - June Mazers Memorial Service Baltimore, MD, 18 January 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 2)
    A jewish service to commemorate Mazer's life.
  - Barbara Grier at Mazer Collection, 22 April 1990; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 3)
    Grier reads at and discusses the Mazer archive
  - Bunny McCullouch on Mazer Collection and Lesbian Sisters, 6 September 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 4)
    Radio interview with Bunny MacCulloch
  - Ret-Bunny-Judy Talk about Butch-Fem-Kiki and Old Days for SCWU Skit, April 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 5-6)
    comparison of lesbian cultural politics
  - Skeptics Brunch How Did you Meet Bunny?, 19 February 1989; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 7)
    A lunch commemorating Bunny MacCulloch
  - Myra Riddell Interview with Bunny MacCullouch, 12 April 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 8-9)
    Interview on issues of homophobia in relationships
  - Pat Denslow and Bunny McCullouch on Age, 19 September 1981; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 10)
    Discussion with Pat Denslow and Bunny McCullouch on Age
  - Bunny Interviews Claudia McMullen, January 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 11)
    Short Interview
    Part of transcript included in box
  - no14 Autobiography tape 1 of 3 J. Phelps and B MacCulloch, April 1982; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 12)
  - Bunny MacCullouch Interview for Lesbian News, 25 January 1986; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 13)
    Interview for Lesbian News
  - June Mazers Memorial Service at BCC, California, 22 January 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 14)
    Jewish service for Mazer
  - June Mazer and Myra Riddell doing self hypnosis, 31 August 1985; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 15)
    tape of self-hypnosis session
  - Bunny MacCulloch on Mazer Collection, 6 September 1987; audio cassette tape (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 16)
    MacCulloch discusses the Mazer archive